Guide to the Bernhard Knollenberg Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence (Chronological), 1560-1943; Series I; 5.5 linear feet (13 Boxes)
  - Notes on Joel Barlow and his relation to Aaron Burr, undated (Box 13, Folder 1208)
  - Poem beginning "Ah say, Sweet Lizzie…" sent to family by Homer Curtiss (Nov. 7, 1863), undated (Box 13, Folder 1209)
- General File (Alphabetical), 1747-1940; Series II; .75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  Series II contains letters, diaries, addresses, papers and a printed book. The material is listed by author's name, and is arranged chronologically.
  Included are two volumes of papers and letters by Francois Alexandre-Frederick La Rochefoucauld Liancourt, writings of Seth Reynolds, a book on the Civil War by Theodore F. Vail and diaries of Alfred Brammer, English workman.
  See Also: Series I for correspondence of Seth Reynolds.
  - La Rochefoucauld Liancourt, Francois Alexandre-Frederick; Miscellaneous addresses, letters, papers arranged and numbered to form continuous volume; Part 1, pages 1-217, (1747-1827) (Box 14, Folder 1210)
  - La Rochefoucauld Liancourt, Francois Alexandre-Frederick; Miscellaneous addresses, letters, papers arranged and numbered to form continuous volume; Part II, pages 218-411, (1747-1827) (Box 14, Folder 1211)
  - Reynolds, Seth Wiard (1840-1862); "Hotch-Potch"And Other Tales", diary and writings, 1858, 1860-1862 (Box 14, Folder 1212)
  - Vail, Theodore F., History of the 2nd Connecticut Volunteer Heavy Artillery, 1868 (Box 14, Folder 1213)
  - Brammer, Alfred (Worksop, Nottingham, England); Diaries (mainly concerning weather), 1901-1912 (Box 14, Folder 1214-1215)
  - Brammer, Alfred (Worksop, Nottingham, England); Diaries, 1913-1915, 1918-1940 (Box 15, Folder 1216-1220)